[{"id": 2795, "question": "There are many acceptable varieties of English throughout the world. Whichever variety is used in your country, the most important thing is that students' pronunciation must be good enough for another person to understand what they are trying to say. In a PPP lesson, teachers naturally include a good model of the pronunciation when they are presenting new vocabulary, grammar or functional language. It is important to start by helping your students recognize sounds before you expect them to produce them. Spoken British English has 44 sounds, but there are only 26 letters in the alphabet for written English. This sometimes makes English pronunciation and spelling different, so it is not always best to write words on the blackboard at the early stages. Also, some sounds in English do not exis...\n\nQ: The passage is most probably from   _  .", "options": ["a book for English learning", "a book for English teaching", "an ad for English teaching", "a grammar book for English learning"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2259, "question": "From Nigerian science fiction to a time-travelling serial killer, Brittle Paper selects the best works of fiction from the continent to inspire our inner desire to travel. My Life in the Bush of Ghosts - Amos Tutuola Who wouldn't want to get enveloped in a fog of magical delight? The novel describes the adventures of a little boy lost in a forest. His search for the way back home seem to take him deeper and deeper into secret colonies of creatures living in reality. Nigerians in Space - Deji Olukotun Wale is a Nigerian lunar geologist. He is under the spell of a life-long dream to traveling out to the moon when the mysterious Mr Bello offers him the chance to man a Nigerian space-exploration mission. But like most dreams, what starts out as the magical fulfillment of desire quickly slips i...\n\nQ: The passage is to attract readers to   _  .", "options": ["Read more books", "Write different novels", "Explore the nature", "Travel around the world"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3152, "question": "Paul received an automobile from his brother as a Christmas present. On Christmas Eve when Paul came out of his office, a street boy was walking around the shiny new car, admiring it. \"Is this your car, Mister?\" he asked. Paul nodded. \"My brother gave it to me for Christmas.\" The boy was astonished. \"You mean your brother gave it to you and it didn't cost you anything? Boy, I wish....\" He hesitated. Of course Paul knew what he was going to wish for. He was going to wish he had a brother like that. But what the kid said made Paul quite surprised. \"I wish,\" the boy went on, \"that I could be a brother like that.\" Paul looked at the boy in astonishment, and then impulsively he added, \"Would you like to take a ride in my automobile?\" \"Oh, yes, I'd love that.\" After a short ride, the boy turned ...\n\nQ: Which of the following best describes the boy?  _  .", "options": ["Kind-hearted and generous.", "Kind-hearted and thoughtful.", "Honest and generous.", "Honest and hardworking."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2593, "question": "Sometimes it is difficult to talk to taxi drivers. They must give all their attention to the road as they work out the shortest way to the place where you are going. However, passengers from Wangfujing were in surprise when they took a taxi. The driver just would not stop talking - in English. Organized by the Cultural and Education Section of the British Embassy, \"Dare to Speak\" examines if Chinese people will speak English in \"real-life\" situations. Matthew Knowles, an acting student from South Carolina at Beijing Film Academy, acted the part as the \"driver\". He collected six passengers on Saturday morning, most of whom were female white-collar workers. \"Of course they were surprised at first, wondering why I'm driving a taxi, and wondering whether this is a real taxi, but then most of t...\n\nQ: The Chinese may meet and talk to   _   in \"Dear to speak\" projects.", "options": ["a white-collar worker", "a foreign store owner", "a restaurant manager", "a high school student"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1545, "question": "About ten years ago, a young and very successful businessman named Josh was traveling down a Chicago neighborhood street. He was going a bit too fast in his shiny, black, 12 cylinder Jaguar XKE, which was only two months old. He was watching for kids rushing out from between parked cars and slowed down when he thought he saw something. As his car passed, no child came out, but a brick sailed out and - WHUMP! - it hit the Jaguar's shiny black side door! SCREECH ... ! ! ! ! Immediately Josh stopped the car, jumped out, seized the kid and pushed him up against a parked car. He shouted at the kid, \"What was that all about and who are you? Just what the heck are you doing?!\" \"That's my new Jaguar, that brick you threw is gonna cost you a lot of money. Why did you throw it?\" \"Please, mister, ple...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["Josh would accept the money from the kids.", "The two kids were Josh's neighbors.", "Josh's new car broke down easily.", "Josh was a kind-hearted man."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2039, "question": "When on vacation,what do you look for in a hotel?Maybe you want a comfortable bed, or a suitable place.However,if you want something out of the ordinary and wish to go beyond the mundane, these spectacular hotels offer a stay you won't soon forget! Hippo Point For those who prefer an overnight stay with some four-footed or two-winged guests, Hippo offers unique rooms on the East African plains .The nine-story tower is treated as one of the top 10 resorts in the world.Guests enjoy incredible views of Olodian Bay.More than 520 species of birds gather around the lake,their calls sounding in the air. Dog Bark Park Inn At the Dog Bark Park Inn,sleeping in a doghouse is a good thing! Located near Cottonwood,Idaho,this bed and breakfast is inside the world's largest dog. Guests relax on dog-theme...\n\nQ: If a person enjoys riding horses, he may choose  _  .", "options": ["Hippo Point", "Dog Bark Inn", "The Poseidon Undersea Resort", "The Magic Mountain Hotel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2179, "question": "The modern Olympic Games, founded in 1896, began as contests between individuals, rather than among nations, with the hope of promoting world peace through sportsmanship. In the beginning, the games were open only to amateurs. An amateur is a person whose involvement in an activity---from sports to science or the arts---is purely for pleasure. Amateurs, whatever their contributions to a field, expect to receive no form of compensation ; professionals, in contrast, perform their work in order to earn a living. From the perspective of many athletes, however, the Olympic playing field has been far from level. Restricting the Olympics to amateurs has precluded the participation of many who could not afford to be unpaid. Countries have always desired to send their best athletes, not their wealt...\n\nQ: One can conclude that the Olympic Organizing Committee   _  .", "options": ["has held firm to its original vision of the Olympic games", "has struggled with the definition of amateur over the years", "regards itself as an organization for professional athletes only", "did nothing but stop allowing communists to participate"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 466, "question": "Teamwork is all about working together to achieve a common goal or purpose.Is teamwork out of date?Why it is so hard to effectively conduct teamwork in those things? One way we employ teamwork in everyday lives is by becoming a parent.It is a parent's job to teach their children the fundamental skills and give them the knowledge they need to be successful in life.So why is teamwork disappearing in this aspect of our lives?Well in today's society,we find that more and more parents are experiencing that the teamwork is one-sided thing.According to a 2009report from the US,there are 13.7million single parents raising their children in the US and this amount could be due to the fact that parents are not stepping up and taking responsibility for their children or they don't have the means to,so...\n\nQ: The author wants us to believe his opinion by  .", "options": ["listing some data", "giving some examples", "asking some questions", "analyzing some cases"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1162, "question": "Though I have traveled in hundreds of trains, few unusual things have ever happened to me. But one day in a train something did happen. I do not mean that I was hurt: no one was hurt. I do my work in a hot country far away from England. Every September I go there to do my business, and every July I come back to England to have a rest. So every September I go to Paris and take a train from the great French city to Mendova, and at Mendova I catch my ship. There is one very fast train from Paris to Mendova, and it suits me well. It goes as far as Endoran, but it stops at Mendova for a few minutes to let travelers get out or in. It is called The Flying Bluebird. It reaches Mendova at seven minutes past nine in the morning, and it is never late. A ship leaves Mendova at half past eleven, and so...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["A Train that Is Never Late", "A Quick and Wise Decision", "A Journey to Mendov", "A Bad Experience on the Train"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 740, "question": "How to protect children Web fans from unsuitable material on-line while encouraging them to use the Internet has long been discussed in the US. For some parents, the Internet can seem like a jungle, filled with danger for their children. But jungles contain wonders as well as danger. With good guides, some education, and a few precautions( ), the wilds of the Internet can be safely navigated. \"Kids have to be on-line. If we tell our kids they can't be allowed to surf the Internet, we're cutting them off from their future,\" said an expert. Most kids have started to use search engines. Many of them are great for finding tons of interesting Internet sites, and they can also locate places where you might not want your kids to go. There are search engines designed just for kids. A certain softw...\n\nQ: What does the passage tell us most?", "options": ["Education", "Good guides", "Precautions", "Software"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3362, "question": "\"Hitler and the Germans,\" an exhibition in Berlin's German Historical Museum which aims to investigate the society that created Hitler, has seen more than 10,000 visitors walk through its doors since opening on Friday. Rudolf Trabold, a spokesman for the museum, said there were 4,000 visitors to the exhibition on the first day alone. People visiting the exhibition said they had waited as long as one and a half hours to get in. Ravi Nair, a 73-year-old Indian visitor, said: \"I had to queue for about an hour but it was worth it. The exhibition should help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable.\" Trabold said \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because it was the first exhibition to explain how a man who lived on the margins of society for 30 years, in Vie...\n\nQ: Trabold thought \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because   _  .", "options": ["help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable", "it was the first exhibition to explain how a man from the bottom of society becomes a leader", "people can learn a lot from the exhibition", "people have been affected by Hitler"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3321, "question": "With five breakout games, Jeremy Lin has become the NBA's newest star. In the New York Knicks' 92-85 won over the Los Angles Lakers last Saturday, Lin had a career-high 38 points.A day later, he led the Knicks to their fifth victory, 100-98 to Minnesota Timberwolves.In his previous games, Lin, 23, had 23 points against the Washington, 25 points against New Jersey and 28 against Utah in his first start. Lin is smart.Before graduating from high school in California, he had sent his application to all the Ivy League Schools .He only got into Harvard and Brown, and he chose Harvard.In 2010, Lin graduated with a degree in economics. Lin is the first Chinese-American player in the NBA.He was born in the US and his family is Asian.Although not born in China, Lin has attracted nearly all Yao Ming'...\n\nQ: The author's purpose of writing the report is    _   .", "options": ["to show his support for the Knicks", "to express his love for Jeremy Lin", "to report the progress of the Knicks", "to introduce a newest rising NBA star"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2330, "question": "Teenagers are under a lot of pressure to be thin. They resort to starving, vomiting and eating only diet foods to try and be thin. Television is a big influence on them. They watch shows like Beverly Hills 90210 andMelrose Placeand feel they need to look as thin as the actresses on these shows. Society is brainwashing young people into believing that being thin is important and necessary. Diet commercials are constantly appearing on our television screens telling us that once we lose weight, we will be happy. While you're standing at the grocery store you are surrounded by magazines claiming to have the newest and best diet. Each month another new diet appears claiming to be the diet to end all diets. If diets really worked, then why are there so many of them? The reason a new diet pops up...\n\nQ: We can infer from this passage that   _   .", "options": ["if your diet doesn't work, the only thing you can do is to accept your body image .", "attending a self-esteem class will help you keep fit.", "we shouldn't pay attention to the size of our body.", "what's inside a person is much more important than his/her appearance."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1334, "question": "Simona lives in Bucharest, Romania. She is nine years old and HIV positive . When Simona's mother found out about her illness five years ago, her first reaction was to tell everyone, looking for support. \"That's when I found out who really was my friend, and who wasn't, \"she said. \"Quite a few people stopped visiting me and asked their children not to play with Simona any more. Because of this, quarrels began in my family with each trouble brought about by her diagnosis. My husband became more and more unfriendly toward me and toward Simona. He didn't understand how important it was for Simona to receive regular examinations by a doctor or why she needed proper treatment for her sickness.\" When her mother tried to enroll Simona in a school, the teacher warned her that when other parents fo...\n\nQ: Many people prevented their children playing with Simona because   _   .", "options": ["she had no true friends", "she was a naughty girl", "she suffered from HIV", "she had a strange character"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2387, "question": "After two classes, I started to recognize several of the faces in each class. There was always someone braver than the others who would introduce themselves and ask me questions about how I was liking Forks. I tried to be , so mostly I just lied a lot to appear to be skilled at dealing with people. At least I never needed the map. One girl sat next to me in both Trig and Spanish, and she walked with me to the cafeteria for lunch. She was tiny, several inches shorter than my five feet four inches, but her wildly curly dark hair made up a lot of the difference between our heights. I couldn't remember her name, so I smiled and nodded as she gossiped about teachers and classes. I didn't try to keep up. We sat at the end of a full table with several of her friends, who she introduced to me. I f...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can infer that    _   .", "options": ["\"I\" was really liking the new place.", "\"I\" had a bad memory, so it's hard to remember names.", "\"I\" was good at making friends.", "\"I\" was not interested in what the girl said."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1143, "question": "A Scottish woman has given birth to twins for the third time. Karen Rodger, 41, welcomed her first pair of girls rowan and Isla after having twice given birth to twin boys. \"I still haven't really taken it on board because I was convinced I was having two boys,\" Rodger told Sky News. Karen said her husband Colin was equally stunned when the couple learned they were going to have their fifth and sixth child. \"He thought I was joking and immediately wrote back to say 'this is not funny'. I had to explain that it really was true,\" Karen said. The average couple has about a 3 percent chance of having twins when not accounting for fertility drugs. And with each following pregnancy, the changes of producing twins a second, or even third time, become less. Karen, a dance lecturer, first learned o...\n\nQ: From Karen 's reaction to the news given by her doctor, we infer that  _  .", "options": ["she didn't know she was pregnant again", "she was happy to have twins again", "she didn't think she was different from others", "she didn't know how to tell her husband the news"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2794, "question": "It was 7:00 am in Kyoto, Japan, and the taxi company had just called a second time to say they couldn't find my house. Once again I spelt out directions even a blind person could follow. I glanced impatiently at my watch, and waited. Only two hours remained until my flight left--and it was an hour and a half trip to the airport. Outside, heavy rains were pouring down. My house was so far north in the city that buses pass only here times a day. The telephone rang again. \"Terribly sorry,\" began the man at the taxi company. Then I realized that the taxi company, flooded with calls, could only offer in-city runs. I had heard this happens when the weather gets bad. I shouted into the phone that I had a plane to catch and I would meet the taxi outside my house. Standing in the wind-driven rain, ...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that the driver was   _  .", "options": ["quick-minded at taking action", "a self-employed driver", "unwilling to drive to the airport", "warm-hearted toward people"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3230, "question": "Global warming is causing more than 300,000 deaths and about $125 billion in economic losses each year, according to a report by the Global Humanitarian Forum, an organization led by Annan, the former United Nations secretary general. The report, to be released Friday, analyzed data and existing studies of health, disaster, population and economic trends. It found that human-influenced climate change was raising the global death rates from illnesses including malnutrition and heat-related health problems. But even before its release, the report drew criticism from some experts on climate and risk, who questioned its methods and conclusions. Along with the deaths, the report said that the lives of 325 million people, primarily in poor countries, were being seriously affected by climate chan...\n\nQ: What is Soren Andreasen's view of the report?", "options": ["Its conclusions are based on carefully collected data.", "It is vulnerable to criticism if the statistics are closely examined.", "It will give rise to heated discussions at the Copenhagen conference.", "Its rough estimates are meant to draw the attention of world leaders."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1248, "question": "A woman wears a face mask to protect her from polluted air in prefix = st1 /Lanzhou,China, in December. A new study showed air pollution might put people more at risk for heart disease than scientists had thought. Kristin Miller, a doctoral student at the UniversityofWashington, said chances of getting the disease were related to not only which city a woman lived in, but also where in the city. The study found that the effects of air pollution were often larger within cities than between cities. The new findings make experts suspect that current pollution limits may be inadequate. Scientists examined rates of heart attack, stroke and other cardiovascular events in women with long-term exposure to air pollution. The study involved women over the age of fifty who had no sign of cardiovascula...\n\nQ: The passage mainly talks about  _  .", "options": ["the effects of pollution on women", "how to protect women from air pollution", "how air pollution damages a person's heart", "the relationship between air pollution and heart diseases"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 372, "question": "The cheetah is best known for being the world's fastest land animal, reaching speeds of just over 110kph for short period of time. However, many people know little else about this wonderful animal. The word cheetah probably comes from a Hindi word spotted animal. It is very similar to other cats but also has some obvious differences. Its body is much leaner than most cats and it has much longer legs. People sometimes make a cheetah a leopard because they both have spots, but in fact they are very different. A leopard is far heavier and more powerful, but also much slower. The cheetah's spots cover most of its body except for its stomach and throat. The cheetah's tail has spots and these become rings at the end of the tail. An adult cheetah weighs between 35-65 kilograms and is about 80 cen...\n\nQ: Cheetahs will not fight another animal to protect their food because   _", "options": ["they can quickly run away", "they are very fast runners", "They want to protect their young", "They are poor fighters"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1038, "question": "There are 132 rooms, 32 bathrooms, and 6 floors to accommodate all the people who live in, work in, and visit the White House. There are also 412 doors, 147 windows, 28 fireplaces, 7 staircases, and 3 lifts. At various times in history, the White House has been known as the \"President's Palace\", the \"President's House\", and the \"Executive Mansion\". President Theodore Roosevelt officially gave the White House its current name in 1901. The White House receives approximately 6,000 visitors a day. With five full-time chefs, the White House kitchen is able to serve as many as 140 guests and hors d'oeuvres to more than 1,000 people. The White House requires 570 gallons of paint to cover its outside surface. For recreation, the White House has a variety of facilities available to people who live ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, when did American President first visit a foreign country?", "options": ["Between 1801 and 1809.", "Between 1901 and 1909.", "Between 1841 and 1845.", "Between 1933 and 1945."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 279, "question": "Ask a teacher to name the most annoying invention of recent years and they will often mention the mobile phone. Disturbed by the problems they create, many head teachers have ordered that pupils should keep their phones switched off at school. Others have told pupils to leave them at home. However, education researchers at The University of Nottingham believe it is time that phone bans were reassessed, because mobile phones can be a powerful learning aid, they say. Dr Elizabeth Hartnell-Young and her colleagues have reached this conclusion after studying the consequences of allowing pupils in five secondary schools to use either their own mobile phones or the new generation of 'smartphones' in lessons. During the nine-month experiment, 14- to-16-year-old pupils used the phones for a wide r...\n\nQ: The purpose of the text is to tell us that  _  .", "options": ["mobile phones can actually help students learn", "mobile phones begin to be widely used in schools", "too much use of mobile phones in schools can cause problems", "the mobile phone is considered the most annoying invention of recent years"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 719, "question": "Alice's mother died when she was five. Although her brothers and sisters were loving and caring, their love couldn't take the place of a mother's. In 1925 Alice became my mother and told me that her family couldn't even afford her a doll. One afternoon in December 1982, when I was getting ready for Christmas, I suddenly decided to buy two dolls, one for my five-year-old daughter, Katie, and one for my old mother. Things went smoothly when a friend told me that his dad, who played Santa Claus in my area, would be willing to make a visit on Christmas morning to our home with the gifts! Knowing that my parents would also come to my house, I began to get ready for the most memorable day of my mother's life. Christmas Day arrived and so did Santa Claus at the planned time. Katie was very excite...\n\nQ: Why didn't Alice expect there was also a gift for her?", "options": ["The gifts from Santa Claus were usually for children.", "The gift was forgotten many years ago.", "The gift for her was bought by accident on the way.", "The gifts for Katie were enough to share with her."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1505, "question": "Columbus made four voyages to the west between 1492 and 1504 in his vain search for a sea route to Asia. The mystery of why he failed to find it haunted him and filled him with sadness. Wherever he went to Cuba, Puerto Rico, Jamaica, South America, Panama, down the coast of Central America--it was always the same story. Instead of golden palaces, there were grass huts and palm-leaf tents. Instead of silk-robed merchant princes, he found \"Indians\" who did not have so much as a shirt on their backs. When Columbus explored the West Indies in 1493,he heard tales of a fierce Indian tribe who literally devoured its defeated enemies after a battle. These people were called by many names in the area, including Calina, Canima, Carib, and Caniba. Columbus recorded the name of the American natives as...\n\nQ: The text implies that   _  .", "options": ["Columbus never realized the full meaning of his discovery", "Columbus was disappointed with his voyages", "there was no way to reach Asia from Europe at that time", "Columbus found exactly what he had intended to"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2709, "question": "The word proactivity is fairly common in management literature, but you won't find it in the dictionary. It means that as a human being you take responsibility for your own life. Look at the word responsibility: ability to choose your response, response-ability. Effective people are proactive because they take responsibility. Their behavior is a product of their own decisions, based on values, rather than being a product of their own conditions, based on feelings.For instance, you are planning a picnic with your family.You're excited.You have all the preparations.You've decided where to go, and then it becomes stormy, killing your plan.Proactive people . They realize what their purpose really was, and they creatively have a picnic elsewhere even if it's in their own basement with some spec...\n\nQ: When a picnic plan is threatened by a sudden storm, reactive people will probably    _   .", "options": ["have the picnic as planned", "make the best of the picnic", "complain and give up the picnic", "find somewhere else for the picnic"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1895, "question": "BERLIN(AP)--A tiger escaped its enclosure at Cologne Zoo in western Germany on Saturday and killed a female keeper before being shot dead by the zoo's director,police said. The tiger slipped through a passage between the enclosure and a neighboring storage building,where it fatally attacked the 43yearold keeper,said police spokesman Stefan Kirchner. \"It appears the gate wasn't properly shut,\" Kirchner told the Associated Press. The zoo was evacuated and a SWAT team was called in,police said.But before it arrived the zoo's director managed to kill the tiger by climbing onto the storage building and shooting it through a skylight using a rifle. Kirchner said it was unlikely that members of the public had witnessed the incident.\"This is the darkest day of my life,\" the zoo's director,Theo Pag...\n\nQ: According to the police,what was the direct reason for the incident?", "options": ["The zoo keeper was a new hand.", "A gate was not closed appropriately.", "The zoo had neglected the secret passage.", "It was very dark when the incident happened."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3363, "question": "\"Hitler and the Germans,\" an exhibition in Berlin's German Historical Museum which aims to investigate the society that created Hitler, has seen more than 10,000 visitors walk through its doors since opening on Friday. Rudolf Trabold, a spokesman for the museum, said there were 4,000 visitors to the exhibition on the first day alone. People visiting the exhibition said they had waited as long as one and a half hours to get in. Ravi Nair, a 73-year-old Indian visitor, said: \"I had to queue for about an hour but it was worth it. The exhibition should help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable.\" Trabold said \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because it was the first exhibition to explain how a man who lived on the margins of society for 30 years, in Vie...\n\nQ: Who experienced the German occupation according to the passage?", "options": ["Inge Lonning.", "Ravi Nair.", "Rudolf Trabold.", "Julien Cayer"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1676, "question": "Thanks a Million, Dad I was born disabled.A difficult birth, feet first, my head stuck.By my first birthday, I couldn't stand or walk. When I was three, the doctor told dad I had cerebral palsy .A loss of oxygen to my brain had destroyed brain signals to the right side of my body. But no son of my dad' s was going to be disabled.Every morning before breakfast and every evening before bed, my dad placed me on the bedroom floor to exercise my right leg.The muscles were shrunk and twisted together.Back and forth up and down, my dad pushed and pulled the muscles into shape. But my dad' s exercise of passion didn't stop there.For my 13th birthday, he threw me a special party.When everybody was gone, he brought me to open a large box, it was a-set of boxing gloves.We put them on.My dad kept on b...\n\nQ: The author wrote the passage to   _  .", "options": ["remember his father", "encourage disabled children", "show the difficulty the disabled face", "give advice to the parents of disabled children"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2234, "question": "A new international study shows that some people's biological clock plays a powerful role for their life expectancy, regardless of lifestyle choices. Published in the latest issue ofAgingon Wednesday, the study has found the most definitive evidence to explain why some people keep healthy lifestyle but die younger than others. Geneticist Steve Horvath from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), led a team of 65 scientists around the world to record age-related changes to human DNA, analyse blood samples collected from 13, 000 people and estimate their lifespan. A higher biological age, regardless of actual age, consistently predicts an earlier death, the study says. \"You get people who are vegan, sleep 10 hours a day, have a low-stress job, and still end up dying young,\" Horvath...\n\nQ: How was the study conducted?", "options": ["By collecting and analyzing data.", "By interviewing lots of people.", "By researching previous studies.", "By studying different lifestyles."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 183, "question": "There are a growing number of pet owners who feed their pets on raw, which means, \"uncooked\" meat and bones. William Burk, a pet food specialist from the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), believes that feeding raw meat to pets is against its goal of protecting the public from health dangers, and that raw meat and bones do not have all the required nutrition that a pet needs every day. Recognizing how popular these foods are, the FDA has provided guidelines for producers of pet foods which contain uncooked meat for dogs, cats and other pets. The guidelines give rules to protect pet owners and pets from dangers about food safety and lack of nutrition. Pet owners who feed raw meat and bones to their pets should deal with these products very carefully to protect themselves against possible d...\n\nQ: Those who feed pets on raw should do some necessary cleaning when   _  .", "options": ["preparing raw meat for pets", "touching the food containers", "taking their pets out for a walk", "preparing foods for human beings"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 294, "question": "Children today would rather toy with new technologies. The role of children has changed as well as that of teens. The world has truly evolved throughout the years. Today,a typical day in the life of a five year old is entirely different from what it once was. A few decades ago children used to work. They did the kind of work parents do today. Today there are shows on which children are putting pounds of makeup on and have flashing things all over their bodies. This makes a child want to _ all of their imperfections. They think they have to look perfect all the time. Teens have changed as well. My grandma got married when she was thirteen. Girls who had an arranged marriage had no time to play because they were expected to cook, clean,take care of the kids, and do housework every single day...\n\nQ: The role of children and teens has changed mainly because   _  .", "options": ["new technologies are developing and widely used", "they don't have to work hard as their parents did", "their world has truly evolved", "they look perfect all the time"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1723, "question": "Money might not grow on trees, but scientists have confirmed that gold is found in the leaves of some plants. Researchers from Australia say that the presence of the particles in an eucalyptus tree's leaves indicates that deposits are buried many meters below. They believe that the discovery offers a new way to locate the valuable metal in difficult-to-reach locations. Dr. Mel Lintern from Australia's Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization (CSIRO) said, \"We've found a lot of the easy deposits in Australia in this way. Now we are trying to find the more difficult ones that are buried tens of meters below. And the trees are providing us with a method to be able to do this.\" Using the Australian synchrotron - a vast machine that uses X-rays to explore matter in remarkabl...\n\nQ: According to Dr. Lintern, what helped them find a lot of the easy deposits in Australia?", "options": ["The pump.", "The water.", "The tree.", "The machine."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2030, "question": "Is your family interested in buying a dog? A dog can be a pleasant companion to your family, but if you choose the wrong kind of dog , you will have a lot of troubles. Families should sit down and discuss the possible problems before buying a dog. Even if the children in your family are the ones who want the dog, the parents are the ones who are really responsible for seeing that the animal is properly cared for. If you don't know much about dogs, it is a good idea to go to the library for books about different kinds of dogs, and books about how to train a young dog. In reading about the different breeds you should know that a dog described as very alert may be too active. When a book describes a dog as an excellent hunting dog, it probably means that the dog won't be happy living in a sma...\n\nQ: The German shepherd is a popular dog  _  .", "options": ["because it is easy to train", "because it is big and strong", "because it is powerful and friendly", "because it is alert and active"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2591, "question": "For years, experts have been encouraging people to exercise, using steps as simple as taking the stairs instead of a lift and walking to work, where possible. A recent study _ this advice -- it shows that frequent active exercise throughout the day can have great health benefits. The study, published in the magazinePreventive Medicine, found that just 2 minutes of stair-climbing several times a day can lower total cholesterol , raise HDL (\"good\") cholesterol and improve the heartbeat in young women who do not have much activity during the day.\"such improvements may have important effects on the health of women, since, like cigarette smoking, poor fitness have been shown to be a high risk for heart disease and death in women,\"said Dr.Colin Boreham with the University of Ulster in Belfast, I...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["How to Prevent Heart Disease -- What Do Doctors Say?", "Stair-climbing Attracts More", "Good Health Advice--take the Stairs", "Yes, Exercise Is Good for You"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1394, "question": "Lonely Planet Publications is the largest guidebook publisher in the world. With over 650 titles sold in 118 countries, it annually sells six million copies, giving guidance to travelers in locations worldwide. Tony Wheeler and his wife Maureen Wheeler were the founders of Lonely Planet Publications and its first writers. They put together Lonely Planet's first publication- Across Asia on the Cheap. Originally from Australia, the couple had decided to travel from Europe back home to Australia overland-going through the countries of Iran, Afghanistan, Pakistan, India, Nepal, and South-East Asia, to eventually reach Australia. Tourist facilitres were limited in these countries, so if travelers wanted to go there, they had to eat and sleep locally. Many of these travelers were young and adven...\n\nQ: The Wheelers wrote Across Asia on the Cheap because  _  .", "options": ["they thought they could make a lot of money", "the Australian government asked them to", "there was no guidebook like it on the market", "it was their job while they were traveling"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3219, "question": "When you were a child you had a pure mind which was free from worries and anxieties. However, as time goes by, you're faced with so many problems in life. Below are five techniques that can help you get relaxed. 1. Mind your own business. Yes, please mind your own business. When you start being concerned about things which are not related to you, you lose your control on your thought process, which often has negative results disturbing the mental peace. Basically, your mind starts wandering here and there. So next time an unnecessary thought comes to your mind, think whether this is really something you should be worrying for? If not, keep it away and focus on something positive, practical and fruitful. 2. Surround yourself with positive people. _ negative comments and stay away from negat...\n\nQ: Which of the following should NOT be done according to the five techniques?", "options": ["Stay with positive people.", "Care about the business of strangers.", "Be sincere with others and never care too much about them.", "Believe in the magic power of what the present can bring you."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 756, "question": "Among various programs, TV talk shows have covered every inch of space on daytime television. But no two shows are more opposite in content, while at the same time standing out above the rest, than the Jerry Springer and Oprah Winfrey shows. Jerry Springer could easily be considered the king of \"rubbish talk\". The show takes the ever-common talk show titles of love, sex, cheating, and hate, to a different level. Clearly, the Jerry Springer show is about the dark side of society, yet people are willing to eat up the troubles of other people's lives. Like Jerry Springer, Oprah Winfrey takes the TV talk show to its top. But Oprah goes in the opposite direction. The show is mainly about the improvement of society and different quality of life. Contents are from teaching your children lessons, ...\n\nQ: Compared with other TV talk shows, both the Jerry Springer and the Oprah Winfrey shows are   _  .", "options": ["more interesting.", "unusually popular.", "more detailed.", "more formal."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2895, "question": "Taylors English Language Preparation 2011 www.taylorscollege.edu.au/telp If you need additional help to gain the high level of English language necessary for academic study, Taylors English Language Preparation (TELP) is the perfect solution. Throughout your TELP studies you will be an active language learner. You will be surrounded by opportunities to communicate in English, with friends, teachers, families and local people. You will gain English language skills which you will keep for life. l English: the language of Taylors College Strong English language skills are necessary for success in your chosen Taylors program. The TELP program, delivered in 12 week terms, is specifically designed to provide language training for academic study. Our teachers are fully trained English Language Te...\n\nQ: The TELP program  _  .", "options": ["is popular and thought highly of by students", "is aimed at those who have passed an IELTS test", "makes sure students have a communicative atmosphere", "makes sure students learn the English language for four months"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2221, "question": "The dirt road made our car jump as we traveled to the Millennium Village in Sauri, Kenya. We passed the market where women sat on the dusty ground selling bananas. Little kids were wrapped in cloth on their mothers' backs, or running around in bare feet and torn clothing. When we reached the village, we walked to the Bar Sauri Primary School to meet the people. Welcoming music and singing had almost everyone dancing. We joined the dancing and clapped along to the joyful, lively music. The year was 2004, the first time I had ever been to Sauri. The Millennium Village project was created to help reach the Millennium Development Goals, which were set by the United Nations in 2000. The plan is to get people out of poverty, assure them of access to health care and help them stabilize the econom...\n\nQ: Because there was no midday meal in school,   _  .", "options": ["kids lacked energy to study attentively", "many kids dropped out of school", "kids made more efforts to study hard", "many kids had to go back home for lunch"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 14, "question": "Bungee jumping is an activity about jumping from a tall structure while connected to a large elastic cord . The tall structure is usually a fixed object, such as a building, bridge or crane; but it is also possible to jump from a movable object, such as a hot-air balloon or helicopter, that has the ability to stay over one place on the ground; fixed-wing aircraft are unsuitable because they only stay high when moving quickly forward. When the person jumps, the cord stretches to absorb the energy of the fall, then the jumper flies upwards again as the cord jumps back. The jumper oscillates up and down until all the energy is used up. The word bungee first appeared around 1930 and was the name for a rubber eraser. The first modern bungee jumps were made on 1 April 1979 from the 250-foot Clif...\n\nQ: The purpose of writing this passage is to  _  .", "options": ["teach people how to carry out a bungee jumping", "remind people of the danger of bungee jumping", "advise people not to take the risk of bungee jumping", "introduce some knowledge about bungee jumping"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3164, "question": "What is your favorite English letter? Many of you may say Q. Why? Because so many of you chat with your friends on QQ. What do you like about QQ? What do you talk about? The CCTV reporter, Miss Wang, interviews three kids. Let's listen to what they say. When do you chat on QQ? What do you talk about? Lin yuhan, Xi'an: On weekends. We talk about homework and chat with each other. Tang Xuting, Shanghai: At weekends and when I don't have much homework. We exchange test answers and chat. Yang yuhang, Dalian: Our class goes online together at 4:00----6:00pm on weekends. We complain about homework, chat and talk about computer games. What do you put on your QQ blog ? Lin: I put good articles I have found online on my blog. I also write articles myself. They are about funny things that have happe...\n\nQ: What does Lin Yuhan put on her QQ blog?", "options": ["Some pictures.", "Good articles.", "DV films", "Japanese cartoons"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1070, "question": "Almost five years ago, I announced to my loved ones I was to become a Mrs. Naturally. I then began to wonder about the perfect wedding dress, hoping that it would fit me. Even at the age of 23, I had gone through my share of dieting. I am an emotional eater and I knew that at 5 feet 5 inches tall and 180 pounds, I wasn't at my healthiest. My mother had been doing Weight Watchers for some time and was rapidly seeing results without starving herself. She shared her books with me and explained the program: estimate your daily target based on your weight and other factors, write down everything you eat and move! The longer I stuck to it the more I noticed a difference in the way I enjoyed food. I soon began to like eating fruits and vegetables for snacks instead of chocolate bars and chips. My...\n\nQ: The author successfully lost twenty pounds   _  .", "options": ["by walking and eating less every day", "by only eating fruits and vegetables", "under her doctor's direction", "with the help of her mother"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 827, "question": "Being connected to the Internet has become a necessary part of modern life. Some people actually need it as they cannot do their jobs without it, and others simply feel they need it as they cannot imagine life without it. To think that something that did not even exist 50 years ago has come to _ our lives like this in just about 15 years makes one wonder - just what will the future bring? In 2004, a survey was conducted in the US asking a group of technology experts their opinions on the Internet in the next ten years. 57% of them agreed that virtual classes will be more widely adopted in schools, allowing students to learn with those at the same level and with interests in the same subjects. It's quite possible that, by the year 2030, every child in every school will do all their schoolwo...\n\nQ: The expression \"play a crucial role in\" can be understood as \"  _  \".", "options": ["change a dull role into", "play an interesting part in", "act a cruel character in", "have an important effect on"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1668, "question": "Why does a large education nation like China have so few world renowned scientists as the US? Educationists from China and the US try to find out the answer to questions like this at a forum on the basic education strategy. The forum, held recently, was jointly organized by the Education Development Research Center of the Ministry of Education in China and the Postgraduate School of the University of Pennsylvania in the US. It aims to find out similarities and differences that exist between two countries in their educational system. While some educationists in China keep a doubtful eye to the country's educational system in recent years. Their American counterparts give a positive answer to the basic education in China, saying that it is still one of the best in the world. An American educ...\n\nQ: China's educational system will   _   in the future.", "options": ["help students to study even harder to pass the examination", "apply more attention to quality education referring to systems of other countries", "allow students to pay more attention to their own interest without their test results", "copy the educational system in the US"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 775, "question": "Being able to experience a different environment and custom will give us a new perspective on everything we thought we knew and understood. Maybe, going abroad is an opportunity to look again at not only the country and the people who live there but also ourselves. I had never expected to visit Paris. The French culture didn' t interest me that much, and Paris seemed too big, too touristy, too much. But when I found myself standing next to the Opera National de Paris, completely alone and totally lost, I knew I was in for an interesting ride. I had decided to take a summer history class abroad, and Paris just happened to be where it was set. My teacher eventually found me and other jet-lagged students and walked us down to where we would be staying. Even then, tired, hungry, and feeling di...\n\nQ: On the first day in Paris, the writer felt   _  .", "options": ["lonely in the big city", "bored with his visit", "surprised at its beauty", "interested in its culture"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 84, "question": "Many people hate wet, sticky August, but to some, it's an especially bitter time. A new working paper finds that, March and August are the months in which divorce filings peak. For the paper, the University of Washington's Brian Serafini and Julie Brines analyzed the most recent years of divorce filings in Washington and drew their conclusion: divorce rises sharply in March and August. The result is supported by some nation-wide, anecdotal evidence. Online searches for \"divorce\" and \"child custody\" dramatically grow early in the year, peaking in March, they point out. The authors guess that unhappily married couples schedule their divorce filings around both the winter holidays and Valentine's Day, as well as summer vacations. (More Americans vacation m July than any other month.) There ar...\n\nQ: Which of the following can support Brian and Julie's conclusion?", "options": ["The divorce rate rises sharply in March and August.", "They carried out online surveys and analyzed the results.", "More people search for key words about divorce early in the year.", "Conflicts in marriage tend to get more serious during Christmas."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1203, "question": "In a world with limited land, water and other natural resources, the harm from the traditional business model is on the rise. Actually, the past decade has seen more and more forests disappearing and the globe becoming increasingly warm. People now realize that this unhealthy situation must be changed, and that we must be able to develop in sustainable ways. That means growth with low carbon or development of sustainable products. In other words, we should keep the earth healthy while using its supply of natural resources. Today, sustainable development is a proper trend in many countries. According to a recent study, the global market for low-carbon energy will become three times bigger over the next decade. China, for example, has set its mind on leading that market, hoping to seize chan...\n\nQ: To fully develop the low-carbon markets, governments can   _  .", "options": ["cut public expenses", "encourage energy conservation", "develop public resources", "forbid carbon emission"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2380, "question": "I was in my third year of teaching writing at Ralph High School in New York, when one of my students,15-year-old Mikey,gave me a note from his mother.It explained his absence from class the day before: \"Dear Mr. McCort,Mikey's grandmother,who is eighty years of age,fell down the stairs from too much coffee and I kept Mikey at home to take care of her and his baby sister so I couldn't go to my job. Please excuse Mikey and he'll do his best in the future.P.S.His grandmother is OK.\" I had seen Mikey writing the note at his desk.I said nothing.Most parental-excuse note, I received were penned by my students.The writers of those notes didn't realize that honest excuse notes were usually dull: \"Peter was late because the alarm clock didn't go off.\" The students always said it was hard putting 20...\n\nQ: We can inter that when Mikey was absent from the class, he was   _", "options": ["somewhere enjoying himself", "taking care of his baby sister", "looking after his grandmother", "studying the art of the excuse note"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 390, "question": "We've all felt discouragement at one point or another in our lives. However, when this emotion bleeds into other aspects of our life, it can sometimes be inappropriate or even harmful. I was personally discouraged by an adult during my high school. After telling her what university I wanted to attend, she plainly told me I would not get in. I was completely shocked and angry at her statement. The adult may have not intended to hurt me with her words, but it had an after effect. The meeting made me think she had no belief that I could possibly succeed in the future. After that it caused me to try to avoid any future meeting with adults until absolutely necessary. We are all human; therefore, we can all understand that some days are more challenging. But when people allow situations of stres...\n\nQ: Who are responsible for children's development at school according to the writer?", "options": ["Students.", "Teachers.", "Headmasters.", "Both students and teachers."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2757, "question": "\"I would almost rather see you dead,\" Robert S. Cassatt, a leading banker of Philadelphia, shouted when his twenty-year-old eldest daughter announced that she wanted to become an artist. In the 19th century, playing at drawing or painting on dishes was all right for a young lady, but serious work in art was not. And when the young lady's family ranked among the best of Philadelphia's social families, such an idea could not even be considered. That was how Mary Cassatt, born in 1844, began her struggle as an artist. She did not tremble before her father's anger. Instead, she opposed him with courage and at last made him change his mind. Mary Cassatt gave up her social position and all thought of a husband and a family, which in those times was unthinkable for a young lady. In the end, after...\n\nQ: What in fact was Mr Cassatt's main reason in opposing his daughter's wish?", "options": ["Drawing and painting was simply unthinkable among ladies in those days.", "He did not believe his daughter wanted to work seriously in art.", "Ladies of good families simply did not become artists in those times.", "He believed an artist's life would be too hard for his daughter."], "answer": 2}]